Integration, protecting ecosystems A.
Daniel is reading an article about Jia Long Nature Reserve.
Read with him and answer the questions below.
Jia Long Nature Reserve is in Heilongjiang province in the north-east of China.
It is one of the world's most important wetlands.
The area provides food and cover for a lot of wildlife.
It is home to some rare birds.
For example, about 20% of red-crowned cranes live in Jia Long.
Many birds live in Jia Long all year round, while some go there only for a short stay.
Most birds are active in the daytime, so you can easily watch them there.
Some people want to make the wetlands smaller in order to have more space for farms and buildings.
This will lead to less space for wildlife.
Moreover, if fishermen keep fishing there, the birds will not have enough food to eat.
Now the Chinese government has made laws to prevent all these things in Jia Long.